It's alright, it's alright.
Cousin is here.
It's okay. You're fine, you're fine.
Who do you think you are?
Ling Yu.
It's all your fault.
You just had to open that Cursed Jar!
Look what you've done to my cousin!
I'm talking to you!
Don't you have any manners?
We have to find that little girl.
Otherwise, we can't cure this Coffin Urn Corpse Poison.
Let's go.
You're really going? Wait for me!
Zhang Tianyou.
You wouldn't leave me behind, right?
As long as I'm in the Sheng Family,
I will protect you.
Young Master,
these stairs here are so weird.
Zhang Tianyou,
even though you're just a Wandering geomancer,
you're actually quite manly.
Miss,
our Young Master is more than just manly.
Think about that Imp from earlier.
It dared to touch anyone,
except for the Young Master.
What does that mean?
Extraordinary destiny, feared by ghosts and gods.
Just luck, just luck.
Whoa, a secondary infection so soon!
Go, go, go! Hurry!
What happened to Cousin?
He's infected with corpse poison.
He's already delirious.
Then... what do we do now?
There's nothing we can do.
They had it coming.
Heaven's will cannot be defied.
We can only hit their death point
and take their lives.
Zhang Tianyou, are you really going to kill them?
What? Can't bear to lose your dear Cousin?
That's not what I meant.
I... I was just lying to them before.
It's because the Sheng Family needs the Qi Family's support.
Actually, you're the one I've always liked!
I found a door!
Ling Yu, hurry!
Hold them off for now!
Ling Yu!
Is Miss Ling Yu inside?
Young Master, think of something quickly!
A child turned into an Urn Corpse.
Listen, my ancient little friend.
We have no past grievances,
nor recent grudges.
I'm sending you to your Mom right now
to be reunited.
So you'd better behave.
Dragon-Seeking Ruler
Ling Yu
The red mark on your hand is gone.
I'll pull you out!
Let's go!
Come on.
Are you two having your Wedding night here?
That's twisted enough, I like it.
Go away!
Get off!
Ling Yu!
Hurry, get up!
Cousin!
Did he hurt you?
Don't sit down!
Tiankun!
Your butt's busted!
Oh my god
Not again
Run!
Treasure!
Rat!
Hold them off for a bit.
Let me get them out of here,
then I'll come back and save you!
One yellow talisman,
to jointly suppress and cleanse.
Father!
Tiankun, what happened to you?
What's with your hair?
Father.
Are you okay, son?
Ling Yu!
Mom!
You scared me to death.
You're not hurt, are you?
Father, I didn't fail my mission.
I brought Ling Yu back.
But I couldn't find the relic of the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family.
I'm just glad you're back.
As long as you're okay.
As for locating the Tidal Tomb,
we can talk about that later.
Okay.
You did a great job.
You really did Father proud.
Yes.
Let's go, let's head back.
Okay.
It's this punk.
It's him.
He almost got Ling Yu killed.
What?
Ling Yu!
What did this bastard do to you?
Aunt Sheng.
When none of us were looking, this punk
tried to have his Wedding night with Cousin Ling Yu in the secret room!
If my brother hadn't arrived in time,
he would have gotten his way!
I thought getting a loser to marry into the family
meant he'd treat Ling Yu better.
I didn't realize I was Bringing a wolf home.
If you say so.
That rat is still inside.
Perfect, let's go.
Come back with me and save him.
Save him?
You should look out for yourself first.
You might have no shame,
but our Qi Family still cares about our dignity.
Your Sheng Family really found a good Young Master.
He really does the Sheng Family proud!
Tianting,
let's go, we're leaving.
Yes, Father.
Father!
What exactly happened?
Mom.
We didn't find the Dragon-Seeking Ruler,
and he almost got his way.
How are we supposed to win over the Qi Family now?
I need to hurry and find Cousin to fix things.
I...
Cousin!
You brat!
You've only been here for a few days,
and you've already made the Sheng Family lose face.
With your behavior,
do you even deserve to be part of the Sheng Family?
What?
I don't deserve it?
Then I'll leave.
What?
Madam Sheng.
Your Sheng Family is a noble house,
so why would you look for someone
of humble origins like me to be your son-in-law?
I'm sure you know better than I do.